sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
dareka no kitai ni zutto kotae
are you really happy
homerarerunoga suki nano desuka
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
even if you change to who you really wanna be
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka
will you always have a great smile?
hajimaridake yume mite okiru
dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
sono saki nara itsuka jibun no ude de
and someday, I'll live on my own.
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo katachi no nai mono dake
yes, precious things are never in shape
te ni iretemo nakushitemo kizukanumama
you never know what it is when you get it or lose it
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
Hey! Jeez.
Hey, Pervy Sage!
Weren't you going to
watch my training?!
I'm researching now.
Do it yourself!
All right, then I'll summon a frog,
a frog so big you'll be shocked!
The Summoning Jutsu!
Hmm? What's wrong?
Did a frog appear?
W-Wait a minute!
What part of that's a frog?!
If you don't get serious,
I won't help you!
Shut up! I am being serious!
Then somehow find your Chakra
as if your life depended on it!
That's what I'm doing!
Huh?!
Sasuke-kun...
Hey, Sakura!
Huh?!
It's about time you wake up
and help me over here!
I'm not sleeping!
I'm busy right now!
Yes, yes...
Then when won't you be busy?
Later!
I can't believe it... Jeez!
Painful Feeling,
The Single Flower
with a Wish In It
Some of you have probably
already heard but...
Gekko Hayate's corpse was
found near Kikyo Castle...
What... Hayate?
No way...
That's ridiculous!
Is the opponent Orochimaru?
No... we shouldn't jump to
that conclusion so easily.
The one Hayate was following
was likely a Sound spy called Kabuto...
Well, it's certain that Orochimaru
is trying to do something but...
So... we'll cancel Chunin Exams
and go after Orochimaru...?!
No, he revealed his identity to Anko...
sending us a threat not to cancel.
Not to cancel the Chunin Exam
for which all of the Ninja of
the Alliance have gathered!
What does it mean?
Orochimaru possesses enough power
to take down a small Land on his own.
He's a Shinobi that probably
every land has eyes on.
Moreover, he conveniently holds
a grudge
against this Village Hidden
in the Leaves.
Any Land would desire him.
So could it be...
that any Land in the Alliance
would unite with Orochimaru
and betray the Village Hidden
in the Leaves?!
Well, the Alliance Treaty is at
the same level as a verbal agreement!
As was in the former Great Ninja War...
In any case,
there's too little information
right now.
Let's end these unnecessary
suspicions.
We've already dispatched ANBU,
the black ops to each Land
to collect information.
It's dangerous to act carelessly...
That could be what the enemy
is aiming for.
And also...
I trust all of you!
When the time comes,
we'll bring all the powers of Hidden Leaf
Village together and simply fight!
At that time...
Be quiet about this bruise!
Should I have stopped him forcefully...?
No visitors...?
That's correct.
I'm sorry but...
I know he's been hospitalized,
but no visitors...?!
What's going on?
We're also not aware of the details so...
There's no use worrying about it here.
Huh?
Should I bring get-well flowers?
So pretty.
Oh no!
Oh... How unusual for you to come
by to buy our flowers.
N-Not really!
Why would you care?
Besides, isn't it unusual that
you're minding the shop?
I'll choose quickly.
People don't like flowers with
roots when they're in the hospital
since they don't want to
be "rooted" in the hospital...
So cut flowers are fundamental.
W-What are you talking about...?
Playing dumb won't work.
You're going to see Sasuke-kun, right?
Mom! I'm going out for a bit!
I-Ino?!
I won't let you be the first to visit!
I'm going with you!
A get-well visit!
...Ino Pig!
I'm taking this flower...
One "rose" of love!
That's so cliché...
Then I'll make mine this.
"Narcissus"!
A noble flower that doesn't
succumb to the cold of the winter,
but hopes for the spring and
waits with dignified presence...
with the wish for release from
the hospital as soon as possible.
You've gotten pretty knowledgeable.
I told you I wouldn't lose to you!
Oh, yes yes, so one narcissus, right?
Uh... I need two.
Why? One is fine.
No... One for Lee-san too.
More please!
— Huh?!
— Huh?
Ten orders of BBQ beef!
You sure can eat.
Just watching you makes me feel ill.
Here you are!
It's here!
This is mine, all right?
Don't eat any of it, Shikamaru!
I won't eat any!
What's going on with you guys,
barbecue in the middle of the day?
— Oh...?
— Huh?
Ino and Sakura...
Shikamaru, shouldn't you be going through
some special training or something
to prepare for the final exam?
I am...
Every single day...
Asuma is so persistent.
Actually, Choji's been joining us
in the special training.
Really?
So you took it on?
Yup! In exchange, he's treating me
to as much barbecue as I can eat!
I see...
Oh, I shouldn't have held on
for the Final Round.
Don't be ridiculous!
There are numerous people who
want to participate, but can't!
That's right!
From what I've heard,
they're doing some awfully
difficult things
over at Guy and Kurenai's team!
W-What's that?
Even though we've made
it this far,
to get totally thrashed
wouldn't be very cool...
Aw man, what a drag...
Whatever the circumstances,
we've exceeded
a human being's limits.
So I've used too much Chakra...
Neji, are you all right?!
Summoning Jutsu!
What?! A tadpole again?!
You haven't made
any progress whatsoever!
See how it's bigger
than the ones earlier?!
How the hell should I know?!
So you want to see
Uchiha Sasuke-san...?
Just five minutes.
I can't allow you to visit
any longer than that.
His body still needs to rest...
Yes...
Sasuke-kun. You have visitors...
Two cute young ladies...
Oh...!
— Huh?
Sasuke-kun, Sasuke-kun?
His clothes are gone!
— What?!
— What?
It's terrible! He's in no condition
to be walking outside yet!
Doctor! Doctor!
Sasuke-kun...
No way...
Sasuke-kun will, without
a doubt, desire me...
Sasuke-kun... Where in the world
have you gone...?
Could cliff-climbing be so taxing...?
Damn, my body is sluggish...
Will I make it in time...?
Open!
Huh?
Yo!
Huh... You finally made it here...
We'll search for Sasuke-kun
on our end.
But if you happen to see him,
please contact us.
— We will.
— Yes.
And also... you wanted to see Lee-kun, right?
He's also in no condition to move,
so please make your visit brief.
Lee-kun, you have visitors.
Two cute young ladies...
Oh?!
— Huh?!
Really... even Lee-kun!
Lee-kun! Lee-kun!
Lee-san...
Huh?
— Look!
— Huh?
Lee-kun...?!
Sakura, let's go!
Okay!
200 one-armed push-ups...
If I can't do them,
100 one-legged squats...
190...!
Lee-kun! Stop it!
191...
Lee-kun!
Please don't touch me!
Don't... interfere...
with my training...
I need two...
Why? One is fine.
No... One for Lee-san too...
Speaking of which, Sakura,
did you hear about that Lee-san?
What? Hear what?
Well, that Lee-san...
his injuries were serious and
he can no longer...
continue as a Shinobi.
195...
196...
197...
198...
I'm... not finished... yet!
There's no value in making
an effort for someone
who doesn't believe in himself!
One... one hundred... ninety... nine...
One... One more...
One more time...!
— Huh?!
— Oh!
Lee-san...!
I'll... go get the stretcher.
Please keep an eye on him.
Yes.
Hey... Ino...
Huh?
Why do boys...
have to push themselves?
Don't ask me that.
I'm a girl you know!
Sorry...
The Human... Boulder!
Ninja Art: Shadow Possession Ju...!
Damn it, I don't have enough Chakra!
What's the matter, Shikamaru?!
Have you hit your limit already?
Man! What a drag...
All right, Choji!
One more time!
Who brought that...?
The rose I went to the trouble
of bringing was a waste.
My narcissus too...
Oh... How boring.
Hey, Naruto!
The swimsuit gals have gone,
so why don't we call it a day?
What? Let's stay a little longer!
Come on, a little longer...
Just a little longer!
I'm hungry. And I'm pretty tired too.
You haven't even done anything.
You should be thankful
I hung out with you!
He's getting ticked off at me.
All right, I got it... Sexy Jutsu!
Oh!
What, that's it?
What I want to do isn't the Sexy Jutsu,
but Summoning Jutsu!
All right, all right...
Then try it out.
Here goes...!
Summoning... Jutsu!
I did it!
You should die!
You have no talent!
Take a careful look!
Huh?
See, it has rear legs!
You idiot! Conjure one up with
hands, feet and ears!
Shut your mouth!
Having legs is better than before!
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Two! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Ichiraku's ramen is
as good as usual!
If the training continues like this,
I don't mind doing it forever!
Eat, keeping eating more because
this will be the last...
What? Did you say something?
Do you like the food?
Hey mister, one more bowl
of ramen please!
Good. Just keep eating away so
you'll have no regrets about your life.
Next time:
"Life or Death?! Mastering the Move is Life Threatening!"
Is this sage hiding something from me?